{"id": 0, "inst/question": "Suppose that the value of x is \u22124. What is the value of the expression (3x \u2212 5) + x?", "inst/gold_answer": -21.0, "plan": "Method: Python Program"}
{"id": 25, "inst/question": "A fast food chain raised the price of the beef burger from $5 to $6, and lowered the price of the chicken burger from $6 to $5. Find the percent increase for the price of the beef burger.", "inst/gold_answer": 20.0, "plan": "Python Program"}
{"id": 28, "inst/question": "Alice invested $1230 into a savings account with 1.4% monthly interest rate. What is the balance in the account after one month?", "inst/gold_answer": 1247.22, "plan": "Python Program"}
{"id": 31, "inst/question": "Ivan can grade 25 quizzes per hour. Find how many quizzes Ivan can grade in 4 hours.", "inst/gold_answer": 100.0, "plan": "Python Program"}
{"id": 32, "inst/question": "Taylor makes 18 dollars per hour at her job. Find how many dollars Taylor earns in 3.5 hours.", "inst/gold_answer": 63.0, "plan": "Python Program"}
{"id": 33, "inst/question": "Uri can walk 7 km in 2 hours. Find how many kilometers Uri can walk per hour.", "inst/gold_answer": 3.5, "plan": "Python Program"}
{"id": 38, "inst/question": "A standard computer hard drive rotates at 5400 revolutions per minute. Find the number of revolutions over 10 seconds.", "inst/gold_answer": 900.0, "plan": "Python Program"}
{"id": 39, "inst/question": "Eve typed up a 4050 word document over two and a half hours. Find Eve\u2019s typing rate in words per minute.", "inst/gold_answer": 27.0, "plan": "Method: Python Program"}
{"id": 41, "inst/question": "It takes Bongo two and a half hours to mow the front lawn. Find how many times he can mow the same lawn in 40 hours.", "inst/gold_answer": 16.0, "plan": "Python Program"}
{"id": 66, "inst/question": "Two cars, a Lotus and a Renault, are 635 kilometers apart. They start at the same time and drive toward each other. The Lotus travels at a rate of 70 kilometers per hour and the Renault travels at 57 kilometers per hour. In how many hours will the two cars meet?", "inst/gold_answer": 5.0, "plan": "Python Program"}
{"id": 68, "inst/question": "In the morning, the temperature in Urbana, Illinois was 11 degrees. By mid-afternoon, the temperature had dropped to \u22129 degrees. What was the difference of the morning and afternoon temperatures?", "inst/gold_answer": 20.0, "plan": "Python Program"}
{"id": 69, "inst/question": "The Mustangs football team received three penalties in the third quarter. Each penalty gave them a loss of fifteen yards. What is the number of yards lost?", "inst/gold_answer": 45.0, "plan": "Method: Python Program"}
{"id": 70, "inst/question": "On January  15, the high temperature in Anaheim, California, was  84\u00b0. That same day, the high temperature in Embarrass, Minnesota was  \u221212\u00b0. What was the difference between the temperature in Anaheim and the temperature in Embarrass?", "inst/gold_answer": 96.0, "plan": "Python Program"}
{"id": 71, "inst/question": "On the first down, the Chargers had the ball on their 25-yard line. They lost 6 yards on the first-down play, gained 10 yards on the second-down play, and lost 8 yards on the third-down play. What was the yard line at the end of the third-down play?", "inst/gold_answer": 21.0, "plan": "Python Program"}
{"id": 72, "inst/question": "Mayra has $124 in her checking account. She writes a check for $152. What is the new balance in her checking account?", "inst/gold_answer": -28.0, "plan": "Method: Python Program"}
{"id": 73, "inst/question": "Diontre has a balance of \u2212$38 in his checking account. He deposits $225 to the account. What is the new balance?", "inst/gold_answer": 187.0, "plan": "Python Program"}
{"id": 75, "inst/question": "Don purchased a bulk package of candy that weighs 5 pounds. He wants to sell the candy in little bags that hold 14 pound. How many little bags of candy can he fill from the bulk package?", "inst/gold_answer": 20.0, "plan": "Python Program"}
{"id": 77, "inst/question": "Julian drinks one can of soda every day. Each can of soda contains 40 grams of sugar. How many kilograms of sugar does Julian get from soda in 1 year?", "inst/gold_answer": 14.6, "plan": "Python Program"}
{"id": 78, "inst/question": "The high temperature one day in Miami Beach, Florida, was 76\u00b0 . That same day, the high temperature in Buffalo, New York was \u22128\u00b0 . What was the difference between the temperature in Miami Beach and the temperature in Buffalo?", "inst/gold_answer": 84.0, "plan": "Python Program"}
{"id": 92, "inst/question": "Rey is planning to drive from his house in San Diego to visit his grandmother in Sacramento, a distance of 520 miles. If he can drive at a steady rate of 65 miles per hour, how many hours will the trip take?", "inst/gold_answer": 8.0, "plan": "Python Program"}
{"id": 93, "inst/question": "Megan is taking the bus from New York City to Montreal. The distance is 380 miles and the bus travels at a steady rate of 76 miles per hour. How long will the bus ride be, in hours?", "inst/gold_answer": 5.0, "plan": "Python Program"}
{"id": 94, "inst/question": "Kareem wants to ride his bike from St. Louis to Champaign, Illinois. The distance is 180 miles. If he rides at a steady rate of 16 miles per hour, how many hours will the trip take?", "inst/gold_answer": 11.25, "plan": "Python Program"}
{"id": 95, "inst/question": "Alejandra is driving to Cincinnati, 450 miles away. If she wants to be there in 6 hours, at what rate does she need to drive, in miles per hour?", "inst/gold_answer": 75.0, "plan": "Python Program"}
{"id": 116, "inst/question": "Geneva treated her parents to dinner at their favorite restaurant. The bill was $74.25. Geneva wants to leave 16% of the total bill as a tip. How much should the tip be?", "inst/gold_answer": 11.88, "plan": "Python Program"}
{"id": 127, "inst/question": "A grocery store reduced the price of a loaf of bread from $2.80 to $2.73. Find the percent decrease.", "inst/gold_answer": 2.5, "plan": "Method: Python Program"}
{"id": 153, "inst/question": "Cindy and Richard leave their dorm in Charleston at the same time. Cindy rides her bicycle north at a speed of 18 miles per hour. Richard rides his bicycle south at a speed of 14 miles per hour. How many hours will it take them to be 96 miles apart?", "inst/gold_answer": 3.0, "plan": "Python Program"}
{"id": 154, "inst/question": "Two busses leave Billings at the same time. The Seattle bus heads west on I-90 at a speed of 73 miles per hour while the Chicago bus heads east at a speed of 79 miles an hour. How many hours will it take them to be 532 miles apart?", "inst/gold_answer": 3.5, "plan": "Python Program"}
{"id": 159, "inst/question": "What number is 67% of 250?", "inst/gold_answer": 167.5, "plan": "Python Program"}
{"id": 161, "inst/question": "What percent of 125 is 150?", "inst/gold_answer": 120.0, "plan": "Method: Python Program"}
{"id": 162, "inst/question": "The bill for Dino\u2019s lunch was $19.45. He wanted to leave 20% of the total bill as a tip. How much should the tip be?", "inst/gold_answer": 3.89, "plan": "Python Program"}
{"id": 171, "inst/question": "Two busses leave Amarillo at the same time. The Albuquerque bus heads west on the I-40 at a speed of 72 miles per hour, and the Oklahoma City bus heads east on the I-40 at a speed of 78 miles per hour. How many hours will it take them to be 375 miles apart?", "inst/gold_answer": 2.5, "plan": "Python Program"}
